Let's cover the communication methods.
So, the first one we have is interactive
back and forth.
That's usually always the best way,
especially if it's face to face.
All right, so interactive communications,
conversations, video conferencing.
If you cannot be together, video
conferencing is the next best.
All right, so you can see each other.
Brainstorming coming up with ideas.
All right, push communications we're going
to send out emails, leave a voicemail,
send out a fax.
So push communications is one way sent to
specific stakeholders
who need the information.
Doesn't mean they received or understood
the message.
Pull communications.
So do think a central
repository, we're going to put
all our project information
in SharePoint, for example.
So we still have to push it there,
but the stakeholders will have to pull it.
Pull.
Go get that information.
All right.
So those are the shared drives,
wikis, Internet.